obeus.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Obeus.com - The Democratic Ads

## Privacy Policy for Information Use on this Business-to-Business Website

Preamble

The service offered by the Obeus through this website enables marketers of all sizes to find and connect with customized audiences. With its massive reach and the industry's leading ad customization and reporting platform, the Obeus is able to maximize return on investment for marketers and revenues for publishers while creating an altogether more relevant experience for consumers.

This business-to-business website is designed for the use of individuals and companies that wish to enter into a business relationship with the Obeus, such as publishers that want to serve advertisements as part of the Obeus network or marketers that want to place advertisements with the Obeus network. As such, the Obeus does not knowingly contact or collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.

### Collection and Use of Business Information

We only collect information about our business partners that may be personally identifiable information (such as full name, mailing address, phone number(s) and email address) if it is submitted directly by you ("Business Information"). You will be asked to submit Business Information in certain fields, which will be used for the purpose for which it is requested and in the following instances:

  * Contact information submitted by potential customers or persons seeking information about our services, and existing customers with questions, concerns, complaints, or technical support questions: This information is collected and stored on our servers in the United States, and is used by us to contact you to respond to such inquiries. Such information is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business, but can be amended or deleted upon request. If you have questions about how to update your information, please contact your Obeus representative.
  * Account information submitted by existing customers: This information is collected and stored on our servers in the United States, and is used by us to create an account for you and grant you access to manage your account. In addition, we may contact you to administer your account and provide services in connection with your account. Any Business Information you provide will be associated with your account. If you have questions about how to update your information, please contact your Obeus representative.

In addition, you may have provided Business Information through your Obeus representative as an existing customer. We may assist you in creating an online account and provide you with a dedicated log in/ username to access your account. That username will be associated with Business Information related to your account, whether that Business Information is provided to FAN online or otherwise. We will use your username and Business Information in the same manner as described above.

By submitting Business Information to us and using this website, you, as our business partner, understand and consent to the collection, sharing, storage, processing and use of their Business Information by the Obeus, its affiliated companies and its agents and contractors, as described below. In addition, if you are located outside the United States, you specifically consent to the transfer of your Business Information to the United States.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We collect non-personally identifiable information automatically sent by your browser when you visit this site (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring URLs, etc.), and stores it in our log files. In addition, this website uses different types of technology to collect non-personally identifiable information, including cookies and beacons (also called "clear GIFs" or "pixel tags").

All of this non-personally identifiable information helps us to better understand how the website is used, offer new or improve existing services, resolve technical problems, measure the effectiveness of our advertising to you and otherwise enhance your experience at this site. The use of information gathering technologies (including cookies and beacons) are required for certain site functionalities to work properly, and the information collected is associated with your account and Business Information. If you do not wish for us to employ information gathering technologies, you should discontinue usage of this website.

In addition, we may use non-personally identifiable information to provide offers or advertisements that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive offers or advertisements based on your non-personally-identifiable information.

### Information Sharing and Confidentiality

The Obeus employees, agents and contractors must have a business reason to obtain access to your Business Information. We may share your Business Information with those agents and contractors (including outside vendors such as payment processors) who help us manage or provide our services or help us with the administration of the website. These outside contractors and agents may store some information on their servers, but they are authorized to use your Business Information only to provide us with a specific service and not for any other purpose. We also may share your Business Information with its affiliated companies. In addition, service providers and other third parties such as advertisers may also use information gathering technologies on this site (including cookies and beacons) in connection with their services to collect anonymous information. Shared and/or collected information, as described above, is controlled by the relevant affiliated company or third party and is not controlled by the Obeus; specifically, (i) such information is governed by the privacy policy and terms of use of the relevant other party and (ii) we will in no way be responsible or liable to you for any data breach by such other party that compromises or otherwise affects your Business Information. We use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard Business Information and non-personally identifiable information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized access, use, disclosure or modification.

There may be instances when we may access or disclose your Business Information without providing you a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Obeus, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iii) comply with the law or legal requirements.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this privacy policy from time to time as we add new products and services, as we improve our current offerings, and as technologies change. If we make any material changes in our treatment of information collected at this website, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice of these changes on this website and in this privacy policy.

### Changes in Corporate Structure

If all or part of the company is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the information that you have provided at this site may be transferred as part of that transaction.

|
